leadferret.com 2012-06-09

# Privacy Policy |LeadFerret | Company Directory

The LeadFerret Privacy Policy is our way of ensuring the safety and accuracy of Internet users' personal information, whether gathered on this site, by our clients, or by our partners. We are in the email business and understand the importance of personal information security. We only work with companies that protect the personal information they collect from their existing or potential customers.

How We Gather Information LeadFerret collects information from any and all legal and ethical sources available through only legal and ethical means, including but not limited to the information you voluntarily give us when you register on our website, [www.LeadFerret.com](http://www.leadferret.com/)

You Can Control the Use of Your Information At any time, you have the right to choose not to receive offers from any of our partners or LeadFerret. You can do this by notifying that partner through return email that you wish to not receive such information in the future from that partner or from LeadFerret.

The Use of Cookies A "cookie" is a small data file transferred by a Web site to your computer's hard drive. LeadFerret may send cookies when you visit our site or register for certain services. Accepting cookies does not give us access to your personal information, but we may use the cookies to identify your computer. If you turn off cookies, there may be some features of our site that will not be available to you and some Web pages may not display properly.

General LeadFerret is a business-to-business site and is not directed to children under the age of 18. Similarly, LeadFerret’s services are not directed to nor intended for anyone under the age of 18. Whether for itself or for its clients, LeadFerret will not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from or about anyone under 18.

Opt-Out LeadFerret provides its users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. We offer users the following options for removing their information from our database, to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.  
Email: removeme@LeadFerret.com  
Call: [818-392-4303](callto:818-392-4303)  
Mail: #221, 2961 Industrial Rd, Las Vegas, NV 89109

Orders LeadFerret uses forms for customers to request information, make suggestions and/or comments and to purchase products, information and services. We collect information, such as your email address, in case we need to contact you with regard to your order. Or, we might just want to reach out and make sure you are happy and satisfied with your ordering experience within LeadFerret. We also collect demographic information, such as zip codes, to track just where our visitors and clients are.

The financial data we collect, such as credit card information, is used to bill you for the products, services and/or information in which you intend to purchase. We also use the information to check your qualifications with respect to navigating throughout the LeadFerret Web site. This information will only be used to fulfill your order(s) and will not be shared with anyone outside of LeadFerret.

Security LeadFerret uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers.

The Use of Cookies Third party vendors may use cookies to serve ads based on prior visits to this website. No personally identifiable information is collected by these cookies. You can opt out of third party vendor’s cookies at any time by visiting this page: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Notification of Changes We are constantly looking for better ways to help protect the information of our clients. We reserve the right at our discretion to make changes to this policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and possibly other places we deem appropriate so our visitors and clients are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected and/or the current privacy policy at our discretion.

Contacting LeadFerret If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

LeadFerret  
Phone: [818-392-4303](callto:818-392-4303)  
#221  
2961 Industrial Rd  
Las Vegas, NV 89109  
info@LeadFerret.com
